Guide to the Picture the Homeless Records and Oral Histories TAM.830
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Picture the Homeless Records and Oral Histories
2000-2024
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Picture the Homeless
Lewis, Lynn, (Historian)
TAM.830
2 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes
56.56 Gigabytes in 28516 computer files
1 websites in 1 archived website.
Picture the Homeless (PTH) was an advocacy organization supporting the rights of houseless people in the New York City area. The group was founded in 1999 by Lewis Haggins and Anthony Williams, and was led by unhoused peoples and people who had formerly experienced homelessness. PTH's organizing work focused on housing, civil rights, human rights, and police violence alongside other social and economic justice concerns. The organization waged organizing campaigns that aimed to address the root causes of and solutions to homelessness through a combination of direct action, civil disobedience, street theatre, participatory action research, self-published reports, mutual aid, public education, legislation, litigation, media engagement, coalition building, and the creation of an organizing trainee program. A core value that informed PTH's work held that the people most harmed by injustice must be at the center of leadership for social change. The Picture the Homeless Records and Oral Histories (dated 2000-2023) consists of the administrative records of PTH, as well as an oral history project conducted by Lynn Lewis. The administrative materials, in both paper and electronic formats, document the organization's advocacy and support for the rights of houseless people in the New York City area. These materials document the organization's activities, campaigns, self-education, and overall organizing approach through ephemera, correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, outreach and educational materials, press releases, newspaper clippings, and organizing resources. Specific campaigns concerning police harassment and violence, broken windows policies and stop-and-frisk practices, civil rights, and housing as a basic human right are well-documented. The collection also includes materials from an oral history project conducted by Lynn Lewis, which consists of electronic interviews and supplementary materials, such as transcripts and photographs. The collection documents not only the organization's activities and advocacy, but places the rights and experiences of unhoused peoples into a broader social and economic context of affordable housing, civil rights, and police brutality.
Scope and Contents
The Picture the Homeless Records and Oral Histories (dated 2000-2023) consists of the administrative records of Picture the Homeless (PTH), as well as an oral history project conducted by Lynn Lewis. The administrative materials, in both paper and electronic formats, document the organization's advocacy and support for the rights of houseless people in the New York City area. These materials document the organization's activities, campaigns, self-education, and overall organizing approach through ephemera, correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, outreach and educational materials, press releases, newspaper clippings, and organizing resources. Specific campaigns concerning police harassment and violence, broken windows policies and stop-and-frisk practices, civil rights, and housing as a basic human right are well-documented. The collection also includes materials from an oral history project conducted by Lynn Lewis, which consists of electronic interviews and supplementary materials, such as transcripts and photographs. The collection documents not only the organization's activities and advocacy, but places the rights and experiences of unhoused peoples into a broader social and economic context of affordable housing, civil rights, and police brutality.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into three series, one of which is further arranged into sub-series:
Series I. Administrative Records
Subseries I.A. Paper Records
Subseries I.B. Electronic Records
Series II. Oral History Project Records
Series III. Archived Website
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Lynn Lewis in January 2024; the accession record associated with this gift is 2024.015.
https://www.picturethehomeless.org/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2007 as part of the Other Left Activism Web Archive. In November 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2024, the website was re-added to the web archives. The accession number associated with this website is 2024.016.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Historical Note
Picture the Homeless (PTH) was an advocacy organization supporting the rights of houseless people in the New York City area. The group was founded in 1999 by Lewis Haggins and Anthony Williams, and was led by unhoused peoples and people who had formerly experienced homelessness. PTH's organizing work focused on housing, civil rights, human rights, and police violence alongside other social and economic justice concerns. The organization waged organizing campaigns that aimed to address the root causes of and solutions to homelessness through a combination of direct action, civil disobedience, street theatre, participatory action research, self-published reports, mutual aid, public education, legislation, litigation, media engagement, coalition building, and the creation of an organizing trainee program. A core value that informed PTH's work held that the people most harmed by injustice must be at the center of leadership for social change.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Homeless persons.; Homelessness; Oral histories (literary works); Housing.; Human rights.; Police brutality.; Social justice.; Lewis, Lynn, (Historian)
- Series I. Administrative Records, 2000-2016
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of the administrative records of Picture the Homeless (PTH). The administrative materials, in both paper and electronic formats, document the organization's advocacy and support for the rights of houseless people in the New York City area. These materials document the organization's activities, campaigns, self-education, and overall organizing approach through ephemera, correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, outreach and educational materials, press releases, newspaper clippings, and organizing resources. Specific campaigns concerning police harassment and violence, broken windows policies and stop-and-frisk practices, civil rights, and housing as a basic human right are well-documented.
  - Subseries I.A. Paper Records, 2000-2016
    - PTH Original Missions, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - First PTH Flyer, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 9/11 World Trade Center Response, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Flyer -- "Don't Talk About Us, Talk With Us", 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Flyer -- Kingsbridge Women's Shelter Closing, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Letter from Gary Delgado, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Raging Grannies!, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Public Education -- Homeless Fashion Show, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Flyer -- Economic Justice Evenet, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Flyers -- Early General Outreach, before 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Flyer -- First PTH Meeting, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - First Postcard, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - May Day and Homeless Rally, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Flyer -- Jan Hus, before 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 2009-2014 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - General Wins, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Disorderly Conduct Campaign -- Orientation Packet, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 125th Street Police Harassment Summary, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - NYPD Finest Message -- Hot-Spots and Encampments, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - NYCLU Letter to Judge Regarding PTH Lawsuit, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - NYPD Quality of Life Targets, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco Report, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Chants -- Ramarley, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - World Trade Center, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Employment and Project Letter, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - NCH Support Letter, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Syllabus, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - CPR -- Custodial Arrest Report, circa 2015 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Press Release -- Harassment, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Flyer -- 125th Street, "Plaza" Public Space, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 125th Street Walking Group, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - PTH Letterhead, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Book Project Notes, circa 2006 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
    - Security Culture, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Canners Survey (Blank), undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - PTH Roles and Responsibilities, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 125th Street Task Force (NHEMA Emails), 2015 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Headline Collage, circa 2016 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - How to File a Human Rights Law Complaint, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Right to Remain Silent, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Skits, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Think You Have a Warrant?, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Want to Plead Not Guilty?, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Homeless Civil Rights: Myth and Reality, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - New York City Local Law #71, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 46-48)
    - 125th Street Press, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Broken Windows -- Background and Context, 2003-2014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hot-spot Profiles, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Flyer -- MTA Sweeps E Train, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - NYPD Harassment, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Profiling Bill, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Municipal ID, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - New York City Local Law #70, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Right to Know Act Communications Plan, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Letter to Editor (New York Times), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Press Regarding Lawsuit, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Days of Rage" Manhattan Institute Die-in, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 24 Hour Vigil (Giuliani), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Quality of Life Protest, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Broken Windows Press, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Funding, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Disorderly Conduct -- Meeting Agenda, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Disorderly Conduct -- Fact Sheet, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Letter to Inspector General Requesting Investigation, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Special Prosecutor Executive Order, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Disorderly Conduct -- Washington, D.C., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Know Your Rights Pamphlet, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - City Council, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Press Release (First Demonstration Against Bloomberg), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Flyer -- DeBlasio, circa 2014-2021 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Sleep Deprivation Press, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Press Release -- Torture and Sleep Deprivation, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Letter to the U.N. Regarding Torture and Sleep, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - New York State Letter to Parolees, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Stop and Frisk; Floyd Affidavit, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Property Loss Survey (Blank), undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Civil Rights -- Survey, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights -- Fact Sheets on Voting, Homelessness, and Incarceration, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Civil Rights -- Candidate Questions, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Voting Press Coverage, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Base Building, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Warm Up Exercises and Ice Breakers, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- One on Ones, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- General, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Supplementary Materials, 2004, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Leadership Development, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Campaign Development, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Solidarity Training, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Outreach, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Organizing 101 for Cooper Square, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Organizing Glossary, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Power Analysis, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Power Analysis Chain of Communication, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Meeting Facilitation, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Description, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Homeless Organizing Academy -- Tactical Team, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Natural Human Right to Housing, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - PTH, San Francisco Coalition, and WRAP Meeting, circa 2015 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - National Homeless People's Summit, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Coalition on Homeless (San Francisco) Summit Notes, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - National Homeless Platform, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Sylvia Gina Hunt, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - History -- Anthony's Statement, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Jean Rice Letters and Essays, 2005-2014 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Anthony Williams Letters of Recommendation, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Banking on Vacancy, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - "City from Below" (Baltimore), 2009 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Speaking Engagements and Workshops -- Social Service and Social Justice, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Speeches -- Lynn, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Press Conference -- Response to New York Post, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- Retreat Agenda, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- Appeal to Faith Leaders, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- "Chases Chase" Article, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- Planning, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- Indypendent Article, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - "Housing Not Warehousing" Campaign -- Evaluation, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Homesteading, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Housing Unit, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Housing Development Ideas, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - "Gaining Ground" Executive Summary, circa 2015 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - "Banking on Vacancy" Release at Roosevelt House, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Notes for 040(?) Event (Frank Morales), undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Intro 48 Bill, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Alternative Enforcement Program (AEP), circa 2017 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Intro 48 -- Campaign Development, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Living as Struggle, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Black Panther Party Housing Campaign, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - PTH Biographries, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Jean Rice Letters, 2007-2014 (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
    - Letter to Eleanor Frazier, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - HSP Survey, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Flyer -- Longest Night, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Morgue Rally, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Longest Night Program, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Homeless Children Education Alert (EAU), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
    - General Information Book, undated (Box 3, Folder 15-16, Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - Civil Rights Notes, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - NESRI / U.N. Special Rapporteur on the Right to Adequate Housing, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - Subseries I.B. Electronic Records, 2001-2016
    - PTH Book Club, 2005; TW_TAM_830_ER_1
    - Canners Campaign, circa 2000; TW_TAM_830_ER_2
    - Chant Sheets, 2005-2010; TW_TAM_830_ER_3
    - Civil Rights Campaign, 2002-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_4
    - Coalitions, 2008-2012; TW_TAM_830_ER_5
    - Communications, 2001-2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_6
    - EAU (Emergency Assistance Unit) Campaign, 2002-2005; TW_TAM_830_ER_7
    - East Harlem Anti-Displacement Task Force, 2007-2011; TW_TAM_830_ER_8
    - Economic Justice Campaign, 2004-2005; TW_TAM_830_ER_9
    - Faith Outreach, 2006-2010; TW_TAM_830_ER_10
    - Flyers and Outreach Materials, 2000-2013; TW_TAM_830_ER_11
    - Freedom Party, 2010; TW_TAM_830_ER_12
    - General Membership, 2004-2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_13
    - General PTH Materials, 2013-2015; TW_TAM_830_ER_14
    - Homeless Organizing Academy, 2008-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_15
    - Homeless Peoples Summit, 2004-2005; TW_TAM_830_ER_16
    - Housing Campaign, 2003-2013; TW_TAM_830_ER_17
    - International Solidarity, 2004-2012; TW_TAM_830_ER_18
    - Labor, 2011-2014; TW_TAM_830_ER_19
    - Lead Organizer.Docs, 2008-2011; TW_TAM_830_ER_20
    - Liberation Library, 2013-2015; TW_TAM_830_ER_21
    - Longest Night of the Year, 2001-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_22
    - Membership Guidelines, 2003-2014; TW_TAM_830_ER_23
    - Mission Statement, 2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_24
    - National Coalition for the Homeless, 2003-2004; TW_TAM_830_ER_25
    - Occupy Wall Street, 2011; TW_TAM_830_ER_26
    - Organizing Resources, 2003-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_27
    - Outreach, 2009-2015; TW_TAM_830_ER_28
    - PTH Book Project, 2003-2007; TW_TAM_830_ER_29
    - Photos, 2003-2013; TW_TAM_830_ER_30
    - Potters Field Campaign, 2004-2010; TW_TAM_830_ER_31
    - Press Clippings (Master File), 2001-2015; TW_TAM_830_ER_32
    - Public Education, 2003-2011; TW_TAM_830_ER_33
    - Race and Homelessness, 2009; TW_TAM_830_ER_34
    - Rental Subsidies Campaign, 2007-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_35
    - Reports, 2002-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_36
    - Shelter Campaign, 2003-2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_37
    - Solidarity, 2009; TW_TAM_830_ER_38
    - Survey Projects, 2002-2015; TW_TAM_830_ER_39
    - Translated Documents, 2004-2007; TW_TAM_830_ER_40
    - Videos, 2007-2016; TW_TAM_830_ER_41
    - Youth Organizing, 2010-2012; TW_TAM_830_ER_42
- Series II. Oral History Project Records, 2017-2023
  This series consists of materials produced from the Picture the Homeless Oral History Project. Materials include electronic audio interviews, as well as supplementary materials such as transcripts and photographs. The interviews document the collective memory of PTH's organizing from homeless members and leaders, former PTH staff, and the organization's political allies. In addition to descriptions of specific campaigns, the interviews also document common themes, such as the material hardships of homelessness, centering homeless or formerly homeless individuals for visible leadership, educational strategies, the role of relationships, stereotypes about homeless individuals, a collective analysis of the conditions that lead to homelessness, and a variety of imagined solutions for greater justice in social and economic systems.
  - Andres Perez, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_43
  - Anika Paris, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_44
  - Anthony Williams, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_45
  - Arvernetta Henry, 2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_46
  - Betty Yu, 2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_47
  - Brooke Lehman, 2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_48
  - Carlos Chino Garcia, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_49
  - Charley Heck, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_50
  - Charmel Lucas, 2022; TW_TAM_830_ER_51
  - Dave Powell, 2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_52
  - DeBoRah Dickerson, 2017-2020; TW_TAM_830_ER_53
  - Floyd Parks, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_54
  - Frank Morales, 2020; TW_TAM_830_ER_55
  - James Doctor, 2020; TW_TAM_830_ER_56
  - James Tracy, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_57
  - Jean Rice, 2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_58
  - Jenny Akchin, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_59
  - Joo-Hyun Kang, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_60
  - Kay Samuels, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_61
  - Kazembe Balagun, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_62
  - Lynn Lewis, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_63
  - Lynn Roberts, 2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_64
  - Marcus Moore, 2017-2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_65
  - Maria Walles, 2022; TW_TAM_830_ER_66
  - Nikita Price, 2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_67
  - Paul Boden, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_68
  - Raquel Namuche Pacheco, 2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_69
  - Rev. Elizabeth Maxwell, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_70
  - Rev. Liz Theoharis, 2019-2023; TW_TAM_830_ER_71
  - Rob Robinson, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_72
  - Rogers, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_73
  - Ryan Hickey, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_74
  - Sam J Miller, 2017; TW_TAM_830_ER_75
  - Shaun Lin, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_76
  - Sheila Turner, TW_TAM_830_ER_77
  - Sue Lob, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_78
  - Tyletha Samuels, 2019; TW_TAM_830_ER_79
  - William Burnett, 2017-2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_80
  - Willie Baptist, 2018; TW_TAM_830_ER_81
- Series III. Archived Website, September 2007-January 2024
  Picture the Homeless's website was first captured in 2007 and the blog posts date back to 2013. Their past campaigns documented on the site include gaining the ability to visit graves on Hart Island; raising awareness of the conditions in the Emergency Assistance Unit; bottle and can redemption; and rental subsidy reforms. The website also contains biographies of their Speakers Bureau members, a photo gallery, reports, homelessness resources, and PTH in the press.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements